One of the things I'm working on now as an open-source project
我现在做的是一个开源项目
together with people from a variety of companies all over the world,
和世界各地的各种公司的人一起
is something called the core guidelines,
是核心准则
which is a set of rules,
这是一套规则
that among other things says,
其他的事情都说
"These are the places where you're not strongly typed,
这些都是你没有强打字的地方
where you can get yourself into trouble."
你可以把自己惹上麻烦 "
We're going to leak some buffer overflows and all the other good stuff.
我们会泄露一些缓冲溢出和其他好的东西
However, we know where they are,
但是我们知道他们在哪里
and we provide you with tools that can guarantee you don't do it.
我们为你提供了可以保证你不做的工具